So something I mentioned earlier is that all HTML elements can have attributes.
在之前我们提到过所有的 HTML 元素都可以拥有属性
Attributes provide additional information about an element and
属性给元素提供了额外的信息
are almost always specified in the start tag.
几乎总是放置在开始标签中
So what are some examples of what attributes we might want to give elements?
那么 通常有哪些属性 又应该放在哪些元素上呢？
Well, it varies on the type of element but for
一般来说 它会取决于你元素的类型
almost every element an ID would make sense.
但是几乎所有元素都可以拥有一个 ID 属性
An ID is an attribute that will allow us to programmatically
ID 属性可以让我们通过编程的方式
select and manipulate that element based on its ID.
来选取和操作某个元素
Another example is source.
另外一个例子是 source 属性
Source comes into handy as an attribute for things like an image tag.
source 属性通常会用在类似图片的标签上
An image tag will use IMG to say this is going to be an image,
图片标签将使用 IMG 表示这将会是一张图片
but to tell it where to pull the image from,
但是为了指明图片的来源
we use the source attribute.
我们会使用 source 属性
Another very useful attribute is href.
另一个很有用的属性是 href
It could be argued that href is really the attributes that the web is built on.
可以说 Web 网页就建立在 href 基础之上
Because href is what you use to a link to tell it where to go to next.
因为 href 属性通常是一个链接 帮助你跳转到另一个页面
So if the web is a set of interconnected links that you
如果 Web 由一系列相互关联的链接组成
can follow by pressing on those links,
你想根据这些链接进行跳转
the href is what's sending you all around those places.
你就可以使用 href 属性来完成它
So let's take a look at this with some real code.
让我们来看一些实际的代码
So here we are with a file called attributes.html and we're going
这里我们有一个叫做 attributes.html 的文件
to dive into some of the most useful attributes and see what they look like in practice.
我们将深入了解一些有用的属性 然后看看它们在现实中的情况
So the first thing I might do is just create a basic div and I'm going to give
第一步要做的是创建一个基础的 div 元素 然后我们给它
it an ID, id equals love.
一个叫做 love 的 ID
We might as well have the text of this say, love will overcome.
我们也在中间放一些文字 love will overcome
Now, let's first check that it works,
现在 我们来看看实际效果
love will overcome, we see.
我们看见 love will overcome 已经显示出来了
Now, this is jumping ahead a little bit to the CFS lesson,
现在 我们似乎要开始进入 CSS 课程了
but I'm realizing I would really like you to see why an ID might be useful.
但这里我只是想让你知道为什么一个 ID 属性会有用
So what I'm going to do here is I'm going to
所以在这里我会先很快地
quickly add some style tags which we'll go over much more in later lessons.
添加一些样式标签 会在之后的课程中进一步介绍它们
But now, because I have set the attribute here to the idea of love,
但是 因为我们已经设置了一个叫做 love 的 ID 属性
I can access this div in my style.
所以我们可以直接在 style 中访问到它
We prep end names with a hash sign or a pound mark for IDs.
我们在 love 前面添加一个 # 号
So #love is ID love.
#love 的意思就是一个叫做 love 的 ID 属性
Then, I'm going to say color red.
然后 我们来设置颜色为红色
Now, we see that the text is red because I've used
现在我们可以看到文字颜色已经变成了红色
the attribute an ID love and then I have used the style rule here to set it to be red.
因为我们使用了 ID love 这个属性 并通过样式规则将它设置为红色
That's one example of how setting an attribute can be useful.
这就是属性的其中一个用途
Let's take a look at an image.
我们再来看看图片
So to make an image,
为了显示一张图片
I need the image tag and then I need a source.
我们需要一个图片标签和一个 source 属性
I think I have an image here.
现在我们有了一个图片标签
So I'm going to try just the name myImage.png.
然后我们设置它的 source 为 myImage.png
I feel like I'm missing something but the browser will tell us.
也许我们漏掉了一些东西 但是浏览器应该会提醒我们
Oh, and there it is.
好了 图片出现了
So another example of an attribute is actually I belief width.
另一个有用的属性标签应该是 width 宽度
So let's try changing the width of that image to make it only 55 percent.
我们来试着把图片的宽度改为 55%
Now, you can see we have a much smaller image.
现在你可以看见图片小了很多
So here, it's an image element,
这就是一个图片元素
we use an IMG tag.
我们使用 IMG 标签来表示
The attributes that we added were the source which is where the image is
我们通过 source 属性指定了图片的来源
coming from and the width which is the size that we want the image to be.
和 width 属性来指定图片的宽度
Another attribute I want to make sure to cover is the href attribute,
我们要谈到的另外一个属性是 href
as I've given it so much credit already.
我已经强调过它的重要性了
So if you don't remember that,
如果你忘记了
href attribute is something that goes to the links on the web.
记住 href 属性用于放置在 Web 链接上
The way that we make links on the web is with an a tag.
生成链接的方式是使用一个 a 标签
Because href is an attribute,
因为 href 是一个属性
we put it in the opening tag.
我们把它放置在开始标签内
So a href equals and
href 属性的内容就是
then we want to pass the href the website that we would like it to point to.
我们想要跳转的网站的地址
In this case, we'll go to udacity.com.
在这里 我们设置为优达学城的地址
We want to I like to say,
并添加上一段文字
follow this link to become a genius.
follow this link to become a genius.
Now, when we go back to our webpage,
回到我们的页面上来
fingers crossed, we see our link come up.
刷新一下 我们看到链接已经出现了
So follow this link to become a genius,
来点击一下它
here we are at Udacity,
我们跳转到了优达学城
ready to become brilliant.
一个可以使我们变得更优秀的学习网站
Those are just three of the attributes,
这是我们了解到的 3 个重要属性
but really each element can have any number of attributes and it can be
但实际上 每个元素可以有任意数量的属性
such a strong way to set up your code to be
你可以通过它们来自定义你的代码
customized and unique exactly the way you want it.
去实现出你想要的结果
As you go through this,
在你了解它们时
think about what other attributes you might like to see and we'll talk later about
想一想你认为应该会有哪些属性 我们也会在之后
how to do advance things using CSS classes and IDs.
学习一些关于 CSS class 和 ID 的高级用法
Up next, we're going to talk about the DOM which is the space where
接下来 我们会学习 DOM ( 文档对象模型 )
everything you do comes together in
它是你将所有页面元素
a conceptual hierarchy that is laid out to the browser.
组织到一起的一种概念层次结构
It will both blow your mind and make
我保证 它会让你感到很有趣
you wish you didn't have to think about it, I promise.
会有一些挑战性！